Hi!
I'm Robin with trees-mom.com.
We're crocheting wire to make a Christmas bracelet.
We have just done 2 rows, and now we're going to go on to the third one.
You can stop at 2 rows and just have a thin bracelet, or add another row to make it a little bit thicker.
We've added one single stitch to the end of the second row, and now we're going to flip over the bracelet and go back the other way.
What we do is put our hook into the first loop.
Pull the wire through.
You have the 2 loops on the crochet hook.
Grab some more wire and pull it through both.
Then you do the next one.
Grab some wire, there's 2 loops, grab some more wire, pull it through the 2 loops.
If it gets to a point where it's just not going through, because maybe you've pulled the wire too tight.
If you push the crochet hook all the way up through the loop, it'll make it a little bit bigger, so it'll make it easier to get through.